<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">Salesforce to SAP Account Migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
This Anypoint template serves as a foundation for setting an online sync of accounts/customers from Salesforce to SAP.

Use this template if would like to sync accounts from Salesforce to SAP customers in manner of one time synchronization by browse toting the HTTP endpoint. The template will fetch all accounts by specified criteria and send it as IDoc to SAP to create/update customer there.
Requirements have been set not only to be used as examples, but also to establish a starting point to adapt your integration to your requirements.

As implemented, this template leverages the Mule batch module.
The batch job is divided into *Process* and *On Complete* stages.
The integration is triggered by the HTTP endpoint to fetch all the Salesforce Accounts suitable for migration.
Fetched accounts are passed to the batch as input. In the batch the customer is fetched from SAP by its name.
If it exists, its SAP Account Group is resolved against SAP. If it doesn't exist, then new customer number is fetched from SAP.
Afterwards every such account from Salesforce is sent to SAP in form of iDoc XML where it is asynchronously updated or created.
Finally during the *On Complete* stage the template logs output statistics data into the console and send a notification e-mail with the results of the batch execution.
		</section>
		<section id="running_on_studio">
		
In order to make this template run on Anypoint Studio there are a few extra steps that needs to be made.
Please check this Documentation Page:

+ [Enabling Your Studio Project for SAP](https://docs.mulesoft.com/connectors/sap-connector#configuring-the-connector-in-studio-7)
		
		</section>
		<section id="considerations">
		
To make this template run, there are certain preconditions that must be considered. All of them deal with the preparations in both, that must be made for the template to run smoothly.
**Failing to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**

Before using this template, you may want to check out this [Documentation Page](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/SAP+Connector#SAPConnector-EnablingYourStudioProjectforSAP), that will teach you how to work 
with SAP and Anypoint Studio.

## Disclaimer

This Anypoint template uses a few private Maven dependencies from Mulesoft in order to work. If you intend to run this template with Maven support, you need to add three extra dependencies for SAP to the pom.xml.

		</section>
		<section id="sap_dst">
		There is limitation on maximum length of Customer name in SAP. Therefore this template strips off all Account Name characters beyond 20.
		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">There are no particular considerations for this template regarding API calls</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">
		
**Application Configuration**
+ http.port `9090` 

**Batch Aggregator Configuration**
+ page.size `1000`	

**SalesForce Connector Configuration**

+ sfdc.username `bob.dylan@sfdc`
+ sfdc.password `DylanPassword123`
+ sfdc.securityToken `avsfwCUl7apQs56Xq2AKi3X`

**SAP Connector Configuration**

+ sap.jco.ashost `your.sap.address.com`
+ sap.jco.user `SAP_USER`
+ sap.jco.passwd `SAP_PASS`
+ sap.jco.sysnr `14`
+ sap.jco.client `800`
+ sap.jco.lang `EN`

+ sap.default.accountGroup `ZAG2`

**SMTP Services Configuration**

+ smtp.host `smtp.gmail.com`
+ smtp.port `587`
+ smtp.user `email@example.com`
+ smtp.password `password`

**Email Details**

+ mail.from `batch.migrateAccounts.migration@mulesoft.com`
+ mail.to `your@email.com`
+ mail.subject `Batch Job Finished Report`

		
		</section>
				<section id="default_endpoints_xml">
		
This file provides the inbound and outbound sides of your integration app.
This template has only an [HTTP Inbound Endpoint](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/HTTP+Endpoint+Reference) as the way to trigger the use case.
###  Trigger Flow
**HTTP Inbound Endpoint** - Start Synchronization
+ `${http.port}` is set as a property to be defined either on a property file or in CloudHub environment variables.
+ The path configured by default is `migrateaccounts` and you are free to change for the one you prefer.
+ The host name for all endpoints in your CloudHub configuration should be defined as `localhost`. CloudHub will then route requests from your application domain URL to the endpoint.
+ The endpoint is configured as a *request-response* since as a result of calling it the response will be the total of Accounts migrated and filtered by the criteria specified.

		</section>
		<section id="default_business_logic_xml">
		
Functional aspect of the template is implemented on this XML, directed by one flow responsible of excecuting the logic.
For the purpose of this particular template the *mainFlow* just executes the Batch Job which handles all the logic of it.
This flow has Error Handling that basically consists on invoking the *On Error Propagate Component* defined in *errorHandling.xml* file.

		</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>